hey spring fans today we're gonna take a
嘿，今天的春季歌迷，我们要
very quick look and by the way I should
快速的外观，顺便说一句我应该
underscore that word quick at the Kotlin
在Kotlin迅速强调这个词
programming language the whole point of
编程语言的重点
this installment is to is to see what it
这期是要看它
looks like to build a very simple
看起来很简单
application with cotton and and with
棉花和与
spring and the short story the take away
春天和短篇小说带走了
I'll go ahead and spoil it is that
我会继续破坏它
there's almost nothing extra that you
几乎没有什么额外的你
need to understand in April in order to
需要了解四月才能
be able to use it with spring because it
能够与弹簧一起使用，因为它
just works it's a for those of you who
只是适合那些你们
don't know Kotlin is a JBM based
不知道Kotlin是基于JBM的
programming language it's from its
编程语言来自
release from the it's released by the
从它的释放
folks from JetBrains and they've
来自JetBrains的人们，他们已经
released this separate language
发布了这种单独的语言
naturally as a as a as a language
自然地作为一种语言
developed by the folks at JetBrains it
由JetBrains的人们开发
has first class integration with
具有一流的整合
IntelliJ but there are plugins that
IntelliJ，但有一些插件
allow you to work with it in other IDs
允许您以其他ID使用它
as well and in fact I may be mistaken
以及事实上我可能会误会
but I think the Germans folks actually
但我认为德国人实际上
developed the Eclipse plugin which i
开发了Eclipse插件，我
think is pretty awesome
觉得很棒
so spring by virtue of the fact that
因此春天，
it's a a JVM citizen it works naturally
它是一个JVM公民，自然工作
with any of these um any of these sort
这些都可以
of languages on the JVM that support
JVM上支持的语言
annotations and and objects right so if
注释和对象正确，如果
you're using Scala that'll work fine if
您正在使用Scala，如果
you're using a sale on that works fine
您正在使用可以正常进行的销售
if using groovy it works fine and if
如果使用groovy可以正常工作，如果
using Cottman and so today we're gonna
使用科特曼，所以今天我们要
just take a quick look at at Kotlin okay
快看一下Kotlin好吧
so we'll build a beautiful cotton
所以我们要打造美丽的棉花
example here and i'll build a web
这里的例子，我将建立一个网站
application I'll talk to MongoDB and I
我将与MongoDB交谈的应用程序
think that's you know we're not going to
认为那是你知道我们不会
spend too long today so we'll build a
今天花了太长时间，所以我们将建立一个
simple app but in order to get the
简单的应用程序，但为了得到
cotman support you need to switch to the
cotman支持，您需要切换到
full version and then go down here to
完整版，然后在这里下到
the the language section right and so
语言部分正确等等
here we can see the three well supported
在这里我们可以看到三个很好的支持
you know languages out of the box we're
你知道开箱即用的语言
going to choose Cottman here and that's
要在这里选择科特曼，那就是
it everything else is the same nothing
其他一切都一样吗
else changes down here we don't have to
否则在这里我们不需要改变
do anything else special so we'll hit
做其他特别的事情，我们会打
generate and we'll be given a zip file
生成，我们将获得一个zip文件
which we can open up in our in our IDE
我们可以在我们的IDE中打开它
and I I'm gonna use IntelliJ but again
我要使用IntelliJ
it works just fine and other languages
它可以正常工作和其他语言
are their IDs although I don't know to
是他们的ID，但我不知道
be honest with you how great the
对你说实话
experience is one thing is that cotton
经验是一件事就是棉花
is becoming very popular these days it's
这些天变得非常流行
a it's just it's just gained first-class
只是获得了一流的
support in the
支持中
in a Gradle build tool so you can now
在Gradle构建工具中，因此您现在可以
author Gradle build files using Kotlin
使用Kotlin编写Gradle构建文件
and Cartman hasn't been for a long time
和卡特曼已经很久没有了
well supported on Android which tends to
在Android上得到很好的支持，这往往会
run a generation or two behind in terms
落后一两代
of JVM interoperability so you can write
JVM互操作性，因此您可以编写
Kotlin programs that run on Java one
在Java上运行的Kotlin程序之一
seven for example on Android and this is
例如Android上的七个
very very cool because Kotlin is
非常非常酷，因为Kotlin是
actually a superset of the j of the java
实际上是Java的j的超集
language syntax right it's not rather
语言语法权利不是
it's it's not all the same features but
不是所有功能都一​​样
if you were to sort of compare checkbox
如果您要比较复选框
by checkbox what you get out of common
通过复选框您将获得的与众不同的地方
versus Java you'll find there's some
与Java相比，您会发现有一些
more niceties in Kotlin and and and and
Kotlin和and and还有更多美好之处
make no mistake Java age is certainly
毫无疑问，Java时代肯定是
making progress and Java 9 looks to be a
取得进步，Java 9看起来像一个
nice step forward and and so on but a
向前迈出了不错的一步，依此类推，但是
lot of the features that were excited
许多令人兴奋的功能
about in Java in the roadmap from Java
关于Java路线图中的Java
like the the possibility of having type
喜欢有类型的可能性
inference for variables that is to say
对变量的推论
Val and var that is already there in
Val和var已经存在
common it's already there and it's
常见的，它已经在那里，而且
working and it can use it and it runs
工作，它可以使用它并运行
fine an older virtual machine so there's
罚款旧的虚拟机，所以有
no reason to to delay if you want to
如果您愿意，没有理由延迟
play with these features so let's go
发挥这些功能，让我们开始吧
ahead and look at our application here
向前看这里的应用程序
we're gonna open up our Kotlin
我们要打开科特林
application it's just a KT file right
应用程序，它只是一个KT文件而已
inside of IntelliJ and the first thing
IntelliJ内部和第一件事
you see is we've got a main method
你看是我们有一个主要方法
defined outside of the class and that
在课外定义
may be a little that may be a little of
可能有点，可能有点
a little bit of a shocker for those of
对于那些
you are used to Java we have a
您习惯Java，
standalone function here right there's
独立功能在这里
no requirement that things be scoped to
无需限制范围
a to a particular class another thing
一个特定的阶级另一件事
that you may notice is this open key
您可能会注意到这是打开钥匙
word this is this is a requirement when
词，这是一个要求，当
you're using spring so when you're when
你在用弹簧，所以当你在
you're using spring and common remember
你用弹簧常识
that almost everything you do should be
几乎你要做的一切
open and open in the cotton world means
在棉花世界中开放和开放意味着
that a the class is not final that is to
那班不是最后的
say by default classes and and functions
默认说类和函数
in Cottman are the equivalent of Java's
在Cottman中相当于Java
final key word they're sealed there
最后的关键词被密封在那里
they're not meant to be subclass but you
他们不是要成为子类，而是你
have to you have to explicitly toggle
必须要显式切换
that behavior so it's the default
该行为，所以这是默认行为
whereas in Java everything's open you
而在Java中，一切都打开了
have to use final to lock it in cotton
必须使用final将其锁定在棉花中
and everything is locked you have to
一切都已锁定，您必须
open it for everything for it to be open
将其打开以使其全部打开
the reason you have to do this is
您必须这样做的原因是
because spring in order to do its work
因为春天为了做好工作
as
如
dependency injection container that
依赖注入容器
provides services it creates lots of
提供的服务可以创造很多
proxies and these proxies are based on
代理，这些代理基于
you know proxies in general are based on
您知道代理通常基于
the idea that we dynamically subclass or
我们动态子类化或
types for you right we can't do that if
正确的类型，如果我们不能这样做
your your methods are final so you'll
您的方法是最终的，所以您将
have the same limitation if you were to
如果您要
make all of your code in Java final
使您所有的Java代码最终定稿
you'd find you'd find trouble working
你会发现工作中遇到麻烦
with spring as well there right and it's
春天也在那里，这是
not too spring I mean any other
不太春天，我的意思是其他
framework that does any kind of
做任何形式的框架
reflection like hibernator or or indeed
像冬眠者一样的倒影
any almost anything will have trouble
几乎所有东西都会有麻烦
with these kinds of types so open is the
具有这些类型，因此开放
is the default and that's I think the
是默认值，那是我认为
one bit of extra verbosity that you
一点多余的话
would get by when you by moving to this
当您移动到此位置时，将会通过
to the common language but it is a
通用语言，但这是一个
overall I think a very concise language
总的来说，我认为这是一种非常简洁的语言
so let's go ahead and try it we're gonna
因此，让我们继续尝试，我们将
go ahead and build a simple application
继续并构建一个简单的应用程序
we'll have an entity an open entity a
我们将有一个实体，一个开放实体
data entity that it's gonna be actually
实际上是数据实体
we're gonna create a type we're gonna
我们将创建一个类型
create a type called a person and this
创建一个叫做人的类型
person is a class right that we want to
人是我们想要的阶级权利
implement but this this class is a is
实现，但是这个类是一个
just a POJO it's gonna have D it's gonna
只是一个POJO，它将拥有D
have field that were in a store in the
有在商店中的字段
database using spring data MongoDB and
使用Spring数据MongoDB的数据库和
so while I could just make it a class
所以虽然我可以上一堂课
like this what I really want is I want a
这样我真正想要的是我想要一个
class that has fields and I want getters
有字段的类，我要吸气剂
and setters and I want to a few
和二传手，我想一些
constructors and I want a two string
构造函数，我想要两个字符串
method and a copy method and I want all
方法和复制方法，我要全部
that sort of stuff right so Kaufman has
这样的东西，所以考夫曼有
a special kind of entity of a special
特殊实体的特殊种类
kind of class for that called a data
所谓的数据类
class right and so data classes are very
类权利，因此数据类非常
convenient they expect a constructor and
他们期望构造函数和
so here too is another difference
所以这也是另一个区别
between what you've seen in the J and
您在J和
Java versus a more modern jvm languages
Java与更现代的jvm语言
is that we can define the constructor in
是我们可以在
the class definition right the primary
类定义权是主要的
constructor secondary constructors take
构造函数辅助构造函数
another form but for data classes we
另一种形式，但对于数据类，我们
this is very convenient right in the
这是非常方便的
constructor we can define the fields
构造函数，我们可以定义字段
that are expected so I'm going to say
那是预期的，所以我要说
that I expect a mutable field for the
我期望一个可变的领域
first name and a mutable field for the
名字和一个可变字段
last name in a mutable field for the ID
ID的可变字段中的姓氏
well in in in carlin it's you have to go
好在卡林，这是你必须去的
out of your way to make things mutable
使事情变得易变
right
对
by default everything is immutable so if
默认情况下，所有内容都是不可变的，因此，如果
you want to express that a value can be
您想表达一个价值可以是
changed you must use a specific type of
更改后，您必须使用特定类型的
prefix var whereas a value that can't be
前缀var而不能是
changed that's constant after it's been
改变后一直不变
initialized that is is Val right so this
初始化是Val对，所以这
is a this is the equivalent of saying
这是一个等同于说
final int I equals 10 right you can it's
final int我等于10对，你可以
it's going to always be 10 you can't
它永远是10，你不能
change it once it's been initialized so
一旦初始化就更改它
we want this to be a we want this to be
我们希望这是一个我们希望这是
to be mutable and by the way Kotlin data
可变并附带Kotlin数据
classes will create a setter for us as
类将为我们创建一个二传手
well that also changes what is generated
好，这也改变了产生的东西
for us automatically by the compiler so
由编译器自动为我们
we're gonna create a var first named
我们将创建一个名为var的变量
field and we declare the type after the
字段，然后在
variable name right this is a pretty
变量名对，这很漂亮
common convention pascal convention for
通用约定pascal约定
for naming things so we're gonna say
为事物命名，所以我们要说
that we have a first name now this name
现在我们有了一个名字
may be no right var is not the same you
可能不正确var与您不同
know the fact that it may be changed is
知道它可能会改变的事实是
not the same as the idea that it may be
与可能的想法不同
no so we need to to say that it may
不，所以我们需要说
optionally be null so we will use this
可以为null，因此我们将使用它
this question mark operator to signal
这个问号运算符来表示
that ok then we're gonna save our last
好的，那我们要保存我们的最后一个
and we'll say that's a string as well
我们会说这也是一个字符串
question mark equals null and then we're
问号等于null，然后我们
gonna create an ID so ID and our string
要创建一个ID，以便ID和我们的字符串
you know it's again it's another string
你知道这又是另一个字符串
well we know now what I'm doing is I'm
好吧，我们现在知道我在做什么
saying I've got three fields here of our
说我在这里有三个领域
first last and ID
优先和ID
these are mutable they may change maybe
这些都是可变的，他们可能会改变
maybe changed there of type string and
也许在那里改变类型的字符串和
they have default values right so I'm
他们有正确的默认值，所以我
assigning Knowle to them but you could
将Knowle分配给他们，但您可以
assign them you know some arbitrary
给他们分配你知道一些任意的
string right it could be whatever that
正确的字符串可能是
would be the default value in this case
在这种情况下将是默认值
but uh it suffice is for us to just
但这对我们来说就足够了
leave it as is right there right so we
离开它就在右边，所以我们
and that's it that's that's all we need
这就是我们所需要的
to do for first today you know usefully
今天要做的第一件事你很有用
define this class we can annotate it as
定义这个类，我们可以将其注释为
we would anything else so we're gonna
我们会别的，所以我们要
make this a the ID field and we'll call
将其设为ID字段，我们将调用
this a spring data document okay and
这是一个 spring data 文件，还可以
there we go
我们去
we don't have to do any code generation
我们不必执行任何代码生成
no command n inside of intelligence
智能内无命令
generate getters and setters and
生成获取器和设置器，以及
constructors and to string methods and
构造函数以及字符串方法和
equals methods all that is just done for
等于方法刚完成的所有工作
us and now we can get to the business of
我们，现在我们可以从事
of actually working with the database so
实际使用数据库的过程
I'll create a
我将创建一个
right as you would normally so okay to a
对，就像通常情况下对
person repository spring data person
人员资料库 spring data 人员
repository and I'm gonna subclass the
仓库，我要继承
Jaypee repository in order to do that
Jaypee储存库就是为了做到这一点
and use the colon operator we have a
并使用冒号运算符
unified syntax for both subtyping and
子类型和子类型的统一语法
implementation of interfaces so I'll say
接口的实现，所以我会说
JP repot as Mongo repository rather
JP仓库，而不是Mongo仓库
sorry Mongo repository for entities a
对不起，Mongo实体存储库
type person whose primary key is a type
主键是类型的类型人
of string and there we go that's it
字符串，然后就可以了
right I don't have to even do this
对，我什至不必这样做
although I could in fact maybe I will
虽然事实上我可能会
let's uh let's go ahead and talk about
让我们继续讨论
the interface definition here so I'm
接口定义在这里，所以我
gonna say fun all and I will return
都会说有趣，我会回来
return a stream of person right and this
返回一个正确的人流，这个
is just a Java JDK 8 stream of course
当然只是Java JDK 8流
everything you can do in the JDK works
您在JDK中可以做的一切
here as well I'll use a custom query to
在这里，我也将使用自定义查询
return everything and there we are
归还一切，我们在那里
there's my very simple interface that
我的界面非常简单
spring data will pick up for me and
春天的数据将为我和
implement now what I want to do next is
现在实施我接下来要做的是
I want to create some sample data right
我想创建一些示例数据
I want to put some sample data and then
我想放一些样本数据，然后
use that sample data to you know to have
使用该样本数据来了解
something to work with so we'll go ahead
可以合作的东西，所以我们继续
and implement the command line runner
并实施命令行运行程序
right it's my command line runner
对，这是我的命令行运行器
contract and you can see that I need to
合同，您可以看到我需要
override this method I've overridden the
覆盖此方法，我已经覆盖了
the run method from the command line
从命令行运行方法
where but in order to do my work I need
为了做我的工作，我需要
a person repository right so I'll say
一个人的资料库，所以我会说
person repository person repository
人库人库
that's now a constructor argument now
现在是构造函数参数
you know I've now told spring that I
你知道我现在告诉春天
want that dependency to be provided as a
希望将该依赖项作为
constructor argument and of course in
构造函数参数，当然在
spring 4.3 which is what spring boot 1.4
spring 4.3是spring boot 1.4
is using we don't even need to provide
正在使用，我们甚至不需要提供
the auto white annotation for that right
该权利的自动白色注释
so this will work right this is the
所以这将正常工作，这是
equivalent of if I had created a
相当于我创建了一个
configuration class created an exclusive
配置类创建了一个独占
constructor and then and then left it as
构造函数，然后将其保留为
is without you know with with the
是你不知道与
parameter there I don't even have to
参数，我什至不必
define the field right
定义字段的权利
spring will sorry cotton and will give
春天会后悔棉花，会给
me that variable as a field which I can
我可以将变量作为字段
then reference inside of my method so
然后在我的方法内部引用
this step person got repository etc all
这一步的人有仓库等所有
that stuff works so let's go ahead and
这些东西有用，所以让我们继续前进，
iterate over some names and we'll create
迭代一些名称，我们将创建
some sample record I'm going to say
我会说一些样本记录
Phil Webb Dave sire Spencer Gib
菲尔·韦伯·戴夫父亲斯宾塞·吉布
all right we've got just some names here
好吧，我们这里只有一些名字
Brian Clough's L Sebastiao de Luz Marc
布莱恩·克拉夫（Brian Clough）的《塞巴斯蒂昂·德·卢兹·马克（Leb Sebastiao de Luz Marc）》
Fisher there we are
费舍尔我们在那里
so we've got a few records and what I
所以我们有一些记录，还有我
want to do is that you know I want to
想做的就是你知道我要
visit each record so again this is a
访问每条记录，所以这又是一个
good chance to to go through each name
仔细检查每个名字的好机会
I'm gonna map it and here you can see
我要映射它，在这里你可以看到
the map method is expecting it's the
map方法期望它是
same map method as you'd expect from
与您期望的相同的地图方法
from Java 8 but I'm gonna pass enough
从Java 8开始，但我已经足够通过了
function and I don't need to provide the
功能，我不需要提供
parentheses so the the map syntax if I
括号，因此地图语法（如果我
want to I can just print I can I can do
想要我可以打印就可以
something with the implicit parameter
带有隐式参数的东西
right this is actually a lambda that I'm
对，这实际上是我的lambda
going to provide it hasn't it's got one
要提供它没有它有一个
parameter called it I t that's the
参数称为I t
default implicit parameter I can give it
我可以给它默认的隐式参数
a name I can say FN right for first an
我可以说FN首先适合
asset last name and then I can delimit
资产姓氏，然后我可以定界
the the parameter block from the rest of
来自其余部分的参数块
the the method lambda block by using
通过使用方法lambda块
that arrow syntax I'm saying FN I'm
我说的箭头语法FN我是
gonna down map FN by splitting it in
通过将FN分解成地图
half right the last statement elastics
最后声明的一半正确
you know sort of expression in the in
你知道那种表达
the block is which is what's returned by
该块是由什么返回的
the way so I don't have to explicitly
这样我就不必显式地
return anything so there's that and then
返回任何东西，所以有然后
I'm gonna I want to visit every single
我要去拜访每一个人
one of those records the two poles if
其中之一记录了两个极点，如果
you will like this and I want to save
你会喜欢这样，我想保存
some data in the repository so I'll say
存储库中的一些数据，所以我会说
new person I don't need to create new
我不需要创建新的新人
person I just say person and then I
我只是说一个人然后我
write some records so the the first name
写一些记录，所以名字
is tuple of 0 second name is you know
是0名字的元组吗？
the last name the family name is tuple
姓氏是姓氏
of one and the ID is automatically
之一，ID自动
provided for us right spring data will
提供给我们正确的弹簧数据将
do that for us so we don't need to
为我们做到这一点，所以我们不需要
implement that that's the another thing
实现那是另一回事
about this these optional default
关于这些可选的默认
parameters it's like having a multiple
参数就像有多个
different constructors right I could
我可以使用不同的构造函数
have a constructor that takes one field
有一个占用一个字段的构造函数
or constructor that takes two fields or
或采用两个字段的构造函数或
two constructed
两个构造
takes all three and that's just implied
拿了所有三个，这只是暗示
for us right
对我们来说
we don't we only have one sort of
我们不只有一种
constructor here we don't have to worry
这里的构造函数，我们不必担心
about providing all these overloads and
关于提供所有这些重载和
all that stuff all that's done for us
所有这些为我们完成的事情
automatically by having common so now I
通过拥有共同点而自动完成，现在我
can visit my repository and I can say
可以访问我的存储库，我可以说
let's find all the records or or even
让我们找到所有记录，甚至
better let's just find them all in
最好让我们把它们全部找到
consumer as a stream and I'll visit each
消费者作为流，我将去参观
one now printout it right where it in
现在将其打印在正确的位置
this case is the as I say the implied
正如我所说的，这种情况是
parameter for the lambda so just in case
lambda的参数，以防万一
I have any existing data in the database
我数据库中有任何现有数据
I'll delete all of them ok now you may
我会全部删除，现在可以
have noticed a few default types that
已经注意到一些默认类型
are returned here so for example void in
在这里返回，例如在无效
Java this Java void in the
Java这个Java无效
auto-completion
自动完成
we're led to believe that it's units
我们被认为是单位
right so that's the default
对，所以这是默认设置
that's how Kotlin talks about void in
Kotlin就是这样谈论虚无
Kotlin there are special collections as
科特林有特别的收藏作为
well so you can say collections let me
好吧，你可以说收藏让我
try a map here okay so Kotlin dot
可以在这里尝试地图，这样Kotlin点
collection these are slightly more
收集这些稍微多一点
convenient types that are optimized for
方便的类型已针对
interaction with Kotlin programs that
与Kotlin程序的互动
that build upon the base types and the
基于基本类型和
inside of the JDK so you know if you can
在JDK内部，所以您知道是否可以
use those great if you can't that's okay
如果不能的话用那些很棒的东西
as well and um and that's it so let's go
嗯，就是这样，让我们​​开始吧
ahead and start it up now we're at we're
向前并开始它现在我们在
clocking in right now at 43 lines of
现在在43行
code and you know obviously lines of
代码，您显然知道
code doesn't really tell you much in
代码并没有真正告诉您很多
about about a program as a merit or
关于程序的优点或
sophistication or anything but I want
复杂程度或其他任何我想要的
you to sort of appreciate what this
你有点欣赏这是什么
would look like in Java and then if you
看起来像是Java，然后如果
if you understood Kotlin sidon syntax so
如果您了解Kotlin sidon语法，那么
fast-forward you know a day or two from
快进，你知道从哪一两天
now and and you're just able to express
现在，您就可以表达
yourself in comments in text would you
自己在文字评论中会吗
be able to edit go had to understand
能够编辑去不得不了解
what's happening here and I would argue
这里发生了什么，我会争辩
that yes I would argue that even if
是的，我会争辩说，即使
you're you're using just regular Java
您正在使用常规Java
and you haven't seen comment before at
而且您之前在之前都没有看到评论
all you'll be able to add a pretty quick
所有您将能够快速添加
glance understand what's happening here
一眼就知道这里发生了什么
because you've got considerably less to
因为你减少了
do you only have to you don't even have
你只需要你甚至没有
to scroll up and down really I mean if I
上下滚动真的是我的意思是
scroll all the way down I I still fit
一直向下滚动II仍然适合
everything in the and the code page so
和代码页中的所有内容
let's go ahead and run this
让我们继续运行
we're gonna use the the Kotlin we have
我们将使用我们拥有的Kotlin
to create a you know IntelliJ doesn't
创建一个您知道IntelliJ不
have it's not quite doing what I would
有没有完全按照我的意愿做
like it to do it's it's trying to run it
喜欢它做它正在尝试运行它
as a java application so I'll say okay
作为Java应用程序，所以我会说好的
and then I'll say that I would run this
然后我会说我会运行这个
as a a Cottman application right so
作为一个Cottman应用程序，所以
create this and you know the
创建这个，你知道
intelligence support for spring Buddha's
春季佛陀的智力支持
is pretty good one of the things that it
是相当不错的事情之一
enables by default is that it'll it'll
默认情况下启用它会
make sure that if you have a web
确保如果您有网站
application that blocks a port for
阻止端口的应用程序
example it'll kill the existing line
例如，它将杀死现有的生产线
then start again that we don't have this
然后重新开始，我们没有这个
poor conflict air all the time so I'm
一直以来冲突气氛很差，所以我
gonna say single instance only I'm going
要说只有一个实例我要去
to hit apply and we'll then run this
点击应用，然后我们将运行它
now compilation is a is arguably a
现在编译是一个可以说是
little slower in Kotlin this is true and
在科特林慢一点，这是事实，
right now it seems to be taking an
现在看来，
inordinate amount of time although it's
尽管时间过长
usually very very quick in fact it's
通常非常非常快，实际上
really quick given all the extra syntax
考虑到所有额外的语法，真的很快
that Kotlin supports but I saw an
Kotlin支持，但我看到了
amazing blog and if I could find it I'll
很棒的博客，如果我能找到它，我会
link it in the YouTube video but I saw a
将其链接到YouTube视频中，但我看到了一个
great blog too there the other week
前一周也有很棒的博客
about Cotton's compilation speed and so
关于Cotton的编译速度等等
on as a measurement of how well it works
衡量其效果如何
with long going projects so actually you
与长期的项目，所以实际上你
can use Cottman and run the application
可以使用Cottman并运行该应用程序
there we go so there's our records right
我们去了，所以我们的记录是正确的
there's our there's our data there's all
有我们的有我们的数据有所有
the records in the in the database I
我数据库中的记录
have in my application right now an
现在在我的应用程序中
embedded web server I don't really need
我不需要的嵌入式Web服务器
and so get rid of that and always start
所以摆脱它，总是开始
just to see if that makes it a little
只是看看是否有一点
bit faster because right now it seems to
快一点，因为现在看来
be crawling one thing that is of you
爬行你的一件事
know worth paying attention to here is
知道这里值得关注的是
that we've got the Kotlin standard lab
我们有Kotlin标准实验室
that's basically the extent of what the
这基本上就是
spring boot initializer is doing for you
spring boot 初始化为你做
when you use Kotlin like this it's a
当您像这样使用Kotlin时，
adding the maven plug-in here and adding
在这里添加Maven插件并添加
the standard library so I've done
标准库，所以我已经完成了
nothing to my environment I've not set
我的环境没有设置
up any custom JDK is I'm not I've not
任何自定义的JDK是我不是我不是
done anything it's just entirely a
做任何事情，这完全是一个
function of my maven build so anybody
我的Maven构建的功能，所以任何人
can compile this code they don't have to
可以编译他们不需要的代码
set up a custom SDK or custom path or or
设置自定义SDK或自定义路径，或者
anything right they just did maven clean
他们刚刚做过一些清洁工作
install so it it interrupts perfectly
安装，使其完美中断
with the rest of the ecosystem with the
与生态系统的其余部分
rest of the team etc and of course
团队的其他成员等等
Cortland libraries can be great you know
你知道的科特兰图书馆可能很棒
packages jars which you can then reuse
打包罐子，然后可以重复使用
and so on so let's see what's happening
等等，让我们看看发生了什么
there's our records there's our data
有我们的记录就有我们的数据
everything seems much happier so there
一切似乎都快乐得多，所以在那里
we go we have now an application it
我们去，现在有一个应用程序
started it wrote data to the database
开始将数据写入数据库
within enumerated that data and and so
在枚举数据之内等等
on so we now have a pretty clean
这样我们现在就很干净了
language we know it's a it looks very
我们知道这是一种语言，看起来非常
familiar temporaries using java or movie
使用Java或电影的熟悉的临时工
or anything else and i hope you'll give
或其他任何东西，我希望你能给
it a shot there's a lot of really nice
一枪，真的很棒
things to recommend Kotlin what I've
推荐Kotlin的东西
talked about here we're specifically the
谈到这里，我们专门
things you might want to know about when
您可能想知道什么时候的事情
using it with the spring boot
与弹簧靴一起使用
application but there are as I say some
应用程序，但正如我所说的那样
very nice syntax features you know
您知道非常好的语法功能
besides type inference which is being
除了类型推断
sort of discussed for the road map from
对于路线图的讨论来自
Java and besides a really really
Java除了真正的
sophisticated type system and the sort
复杂的类型系统和分类
of default support for mutability and so
对可变性的默认支持等等
on there's also some some other niceties
在上面还有一些其他的优点
like for example extension functions you
例如扩展功能
can actually add functions to any
可以实际将功能添加到任何
arbitrary type after the fact so to
事实之后的任意类型
speak gaia so for example if you want to
说盖亚语，例如，如果您想
add a
添加一个
a Buddha fie method right maybe one that
佛陀的拳法也许是
change the way that the JDK is string
更改JDK是字符串的方式
class works you could say function
你可以说功能的课堂作品
string dot beautify and then say return
字符串点美化，然后说返回
or you don't need to return beautiful
或你不需要返回美丽
this right and now anywhere you had a
这个权利，现在你在任何地方都有
string you could say booed if I right
如果我正确的话，你可以说嘘
that's that's just built in on to the on
那就是内置的
to the default sort of string class
到默认的字符串类排序
right now to work on all your code so
现在就可以处理所有代码
now you can have convenience methods
现在您可以使用便捷的方法
instead of having these separate
而不是将它们分开
companion objects and you can do that
随播对象，您可以执行此操作
too by the way right like you can you
也可以顺便说一句
can see that you can have functions that
可以看到您可以具有
are standalone as well so that's another
也都是独立的，这是另一个
nice it is that you can you know you can
很好，你可以知道你可以
model things that are purely sort of
模拟纯粹的事物
functional bits and then share them much
功能位，然后分享很多
more naturally instead of shoehorning
更自然地代替鞋拔
them into this to an approach that may
他们采取这种方法
not work for you all right with that i
我不能为你工作
will wrap this up and I'll see you next
会把这个包起来，我下次见
time thanks so much
时间非常感谢
you
您